A Guide to the Virginia Department of Treasury, Division of Unclaimed Property, 1822-1991
Library of Virginia
- Accession 43250,1860-1983., Extent: 12 boxes. (Box 35-46)
  - Lot 872624 - Papers of Phyllis C. Daniels,1926-1967. (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Lot 874470 - Papers of Douglas L. Vaughan, Sr.,1969. (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Lot 878988 - Papers of Beverly Graham,1977. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Lot 879304 - Papers of Douglas L. Pugh,1940-1969. (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Lot 879304 - Papers of Douglas L. Pugh,1940-1969. (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Lot 881073 - Papers of Earl and Phyllis Ritchie,1942-1973. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Lot 881530 - Papers of Connie W. Ashbury,1941-1974. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Lot 892815 - Papers of Linda Weinfeld,1975. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Lot 899024 - Papers of Robert Cherin,1973. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Lot 902917 - Papers of Elsie K. Oswald,1923-1970. (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Lot 902917 - Papers of Elsie K. Oswald,1923-1970. (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Lot 906828 - Papers of Meddie Craig and Linda M. Adams,1962-1968. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Lot 913946 - Papers of Raymond C. Tumblin,1976. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Lot 917189 - Papers of Brenda C. Wade,1976-1977. (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Lot 917865 - Papers of Donnie W. Draughon, Jr.,1967-1973. (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Lot 923708 - Papers of Carl E. Thompson,1918-1970. (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Lot 923708 - Papers of Carl E. Thompson,1918-1970. (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Lot 923792 - Papers of J. Edward Person,1969. (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Lot 924119 - Papers of Carol S. Flippo,1926-1971. (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Lot 926957 - Papers of the Estate of Noah Reynolds,1967-1973. (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Lot 932021 - Papers of Christopher Knight,1974-1975. (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Lot 941549 - Papers of Fred R. Greenwood,1975-1976. (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Lot 944329 - Papers of Alton J. Smyre,1978. (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Lot 947217 - Papers of Ronald W. Bibb,1969. (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Lot 953230 - Papers of Robert B. Dunham,1948-1975. (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Lot 953230 - Papers of Robert B. Dunham,1948-1975. (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Lot 953842 - Papers of Lewis J. Thompson,1939-1958. (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Lot 963820 - Papers of James Williamson,1945-1973. (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Lot 963820 - Papers of James Williamson,1945-1973. (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Lot 971290 - Papers of John W. Keller,1934-1974. (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Lot 975042 - Papers of John O. Chamberlain, Jr.,1950-1958. (1 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Lot 975042 - Papers of John O. Chamberlain, Jr.,1950-1958. (2 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Lot 975042 - Papers of John O. Chamberlain, Jr.,1950-1958. (3 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Lot 988049 - Papers of Marvin L. Hoard,1953-1961. (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Lot 991386 - Papers of Henry L. Searcy,1944-1973. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Lot 992779 - Papers of William L. Alford, Jr.,1976-1980. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Lot 1000480 - Papers of the Mark Larwood Company,1944. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Lot 1006100 - Papers of Larry and Jane Winkle,1953-1972. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Lot 1006964 - Papers of T. W. Camden,1962-1967. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Lot 1007439 - Papers of Pearl S. James,1966. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Lot 1008762 - Papers of John and Patricia Davis,1972-1973. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Lot 1009552 - Papers of Nora and William Saunders,1962-1976. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Lot 1013986 - Papers of Howard B. Hairston,1946-1970. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Lot 1020530 - Papers of Sherwood Randolph,1966. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Lot 1025091 - Papers of George S. Nohava,1944-1974. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Lot 1029645 - Papers of Stephen D. Buchanan,1973. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Lot 1035236 - Papers of Roy N. Fitzer,1943. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Lot 1035772 - Papers of Arthur M. Eason, Sr.,1944. (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Lot 1038557 - Papers of Stephen T. Jablonski,1967-1970. (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Lot 1039158 - Papers of T. J. Massengale,1970-1971. (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Lot 1059118 - Papers of Vergie Myers,1950-1972. (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Lot 1074508 - Papers of Connie F. Glenn and George A. Donnelly,1975. (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Lot 1082423 - Papers of Bobby Campbell,. (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Lot 1084900 - Papers of Ervin E. Roden,1960-1977. (1 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Lot 1084900 - Papers of Ervin E. Roden,1960-1977. (2 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Lot 1084900 - Papers of Ervin E. Roden,1960-1977. (3 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Lot 1088360 - Papers of Leonard E. Harshbarger,1976. (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Lot 1093931 - Papers of Cecil Massie,1983. (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Lot 1096139 - Papers of June M. Good,1967. (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Lot 1100324 - Papers of Lizzie Wallen,1915-1974. (1 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Lot 1100324 - Papers of Lizzie Wallen,1915-1974. (2 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Lot 1100324 - Papers of Lizzie Wallen,1915-1974. (3 of 3) (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Lot 1117532 - Papers of Jerry Lee Clark,1947. (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Lot 1127211 - Papers of Helen Sutton,1966-1971. (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Lot 1128895 - Papers of Charlotte E. Shuemaker,1966-1968. (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Lot 1129023 - Papers of Carlton Beasley,1968-1972. (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Lot 1135312 - Papers of Robert J. Sharpe,1958. (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Lot 1138189 - Papers of Lilly and Paul Davis,1962-1973. (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Lot 1139259 - Papers of Barbara D. Gary,1933-1966. (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Lot 1139341 - Papers of Ralph W. Wiseman,1970. (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Lot 1140030 - Papers of Billy J. Baker,1971-1972. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Lot 1142605 - Papers of Kenneth M. Davis,1955-1975. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Lot 1154736 - Papers of Ina M. Zimmer,1939-1975. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Lot 1157226 - Papers of W. T. Gillespie,1975-1977. (1 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Lot 1157226 - Papers of W. T. Gillespie,1975-1977. (2 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Lot 1166726 - Papers of Thelma Shelton,1949-1964. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Lot 1173138 - Papers of Eliza Spangler,1940-1970. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Lot 1174038 - Papers of Carol S. Randolph,1957-1978. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Lot 1184988 - Papers of Diane L. Giorigi,1947-1979. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Lot 1187457 - Papers of Barbara T. Bemory,1976. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Lot 1192872 - Papers of Carol A. S. Amos,1947-1970. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Lot 1193291 - Papers of Patrick Higgenbotham,1939-1962. (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Lot 1212853 - Papers of Robert W. Norris,1951. (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Lot 1228277 - Papers of Dorothy A. Pritchett,1976. (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Lot 1239562 - Papers of Roland O. Davis,1898-1963. (1 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Lot 1239562 - Papers of Roland O. Davis,1898-1963. (2 of 2) (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Lot 153224 - Papers of Deborah Sallah,1975. (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Lot 1255285 - Papers of Jonathan E. McAllister,1951. (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Lot 1259878 - Papers of James S. Byrd,1928-1957. (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Lot 1265429 - Papers of Vito Conigliaro,1975. (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Lot 1268990 - Papers of Bruce McCombe,1983-1972. (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Lot 1271064 - Papers of Allen L. Prigden,1975-1978. (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Lot 1271485 - Papers of Hilliard Melton, Jr.,1949-1985. (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Lot 1278900 - Papers of Ann Davis Plumlee,1974-1977. (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Lot 1278998 - Papers of Shirley and William Clarke,1945-1976. (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Lot 1289984 - Papers of James M. Davis,1917-1970. (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Lot 1290460 - Papers of Margaret K. Seay,1947-1975. (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Lot 1307821 - Papers of Sandra D. Harris,. (1 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Lot 1307821 - Papers of Sandra D. Harris,. (2 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Lot 1307821 - Papers of Sandra D. Harris,. (3 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Lot 1309928 - Papers of Harvey L. Carter,1975. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Lot 1316097 - Papers of Basil M. Miller,1927-1972. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Lot 1318428 - Papers of Franklin Washington,1969-1973. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Lot 1318538 - Papers of Corbin A. Cash III,1971. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Lot 1319169 - Papers of William J. Donnelly,1907-1964. (1 of 2) (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Lot 1319169 - Papers of William J. Donnelly,1907-1964. (2 of 2) (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Lot 1334672 - Papers of William D. Lemke,1972. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Lot 1341380 - Papers of Raymond D. Lee,1944-1968. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Lot 1341748 - Papers of Jesse C. Arrington,1976. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Lot 1356752 - Papers of John W. Lester,1965-1966. (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Lot 1358527 - Papers of James S. Hicks,1976-1977. (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Lot 1359282 - Papers of Bill Zimmerman,1977. (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Lot 1376654 - Papers of Norman B. Ellis,1961-1965. (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Lot 1378824 - Papers of Michael J. Krupin,1971-1973. (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Lot 1389713 - Papers of Irene E. Tischler,1917-1977. (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Lot 1403620 - Papers of Irene Perry,1946-1952. (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Lot 1407886 - Papers of Niconnor Jaramillo,1965-1975. (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Lot 1409156 - Papers of Joseph F. McEvoy,1967. (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Lot 1411798 - Papers of Arthur E. Berger,1976. (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Lot 1412766 - Papers of Ronald G. Dawson,1947-1972. (1 of 2) (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Lot 1412766 - Papers of Ronald G. Dawson,1947-1972. (2 of 2) (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Lot 1416114 - Papers of Lindsey S. Hassell,1975. (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Unnumbered lot - Papers of the Hunt Family,1919-1920. (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Unnumbered lot - Papers of Toralf Dahlin,1942-1952. (1 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Unnumbered lot - Papers of Toralf Dahlin,1942-1952. (2 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Unnumbered lot - Papers of Toralf Dahlin,1942-1952. (3 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Lot 312408 - Papers of John E. Eagle,1919-1963. (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Records - Accession 50624, 1865-1988., Extent: 14 boxes. (Box 47-60)
  - Lot 9996 - Papers of Jerry M. Spence,1972-1980. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Lot 9997 - Papers of Elaine Stephens,1981-1986. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Lot 9998 - Papers of Anthony B. Stock,1965-1968. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Lot 10000 - Papers of Terle Associates (John Bisaga and Howard Blank),1973-1975. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Lot 10006 - Papers of Henry T. Myers,1969-1979. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Lot 10009 - Papers of Leon T. Nicholson,1973. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Lot 10508 - Papers of Arthur Wadsworth,1943-1968. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Lot 10509 - Papers of Mary G. Simmons,1969. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Lot 10511 - Papers of William Webb and Sue Whitlark,1947-1972. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Lot 10512 - Papers of Lillian and Burnie White,1916-1965. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Lot 10515 - Papers of William and Virgie Wood,1954. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Lot 10532 - Papers of Troy and Christina Kelly,1960. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Lot 10534 - Papers of John and Linda McLeod,1944-1977. (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Lot 10535 - Papers of Jonathan B. Smith,1980. (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Lot 10543 - Papers of Willie Ann Clardy Womack,1936-1958. (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Lot 10553 - Papers of Anderson Roberson,1947-1981. (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Lot 10557 - Papers of Andrew J. Welebir,1979-1981. (1 of 2) (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Lot 10557 - Papers of Andrew J. Welebir,1978-1982. (2 of 2) (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Lot 10666 - Papers of Callie B. Gass,1980. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Lot 10957 - Papers of Maria Ann Johns,1946-1972. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Lot 10962 - Papers of Victor and Janet Kerr,1943. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Lot 10967 - Papers of Ethel Willey and Reva Akers,1977-1988. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Lot 10986 - Papers of R. H. Rhodes,1926-1957. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Lot 11005 - Papers of James and Joanne Witherow,1970. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Lot 11026 - Papers of Jack C. Lambui,1951-1980. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Lot 11080 - Papers of Donald J. Mayton,1977-1980. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Lot 11083 - Papers of Dennis Hughes,1978-1982. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Lot 11110 - Papers of Frances Nash Farlow,1916-1978. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Lot 11121 - Papers of Ledru Bulick,1934-1977. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Lot 11303 - Papers of Rodney and Rena Stauffer,1950-1965. (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Lot 11307 - Papers of Robert W. Scott,1975-1980. (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Lot 11333 - Papers of Robert Garrison,1952-1956. (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Lot 11335 - Papers of Eddie and Catherine Jackson,1976. (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Lot 11472 - Papers of Winslow Borzotra,1976. (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Lot 11474 - Papers of Doris Moore,1949-1980. (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Lot 11476 - Papers of Filippo Cerlito,1980. (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Lot 11478 - Papers of Cherie Benson Harris,1963-1985. (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Lot 11483 - Papers of Ann Labiosa,1942. (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Lot 11485 - Papers of William and Donna Nash,1962-1976. (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Lot 11486 - Papers of Ned Randall Tolar,1944-1973. (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Lot 11487 - Papers of James Jones,1975. (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Lot 11492 - Papers of Sylvia Zipperian,1973-1975. (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Lot 11494 - Papers of Richard L. Hardy,1945-1957. (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Lot 11502 - Papers of David Lipscombe and Cathy Saunders Napier,1956-1976. (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Lot 11505 - Papers of Gregory L. Maxwell,1981-1982. (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Lot 11507 - Papers of Fredette (Loudermilk) Butler and Steve Scott,1973-1980. (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Lot 11511 - Papers of Eugene Tull,1966-1967. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Lot 11514 - Papers of Jennie W. Popkin,1979-1981. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Lot 11516 - Papers of Nancy L. Wolfe,1981. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Lot 11517 - Papers of William A. Cooke,1974-1978. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Lot 11523 - Papers of Alexander B. Jackson,1966-1979. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Lot 11526 - Papers of James and Susan Sanderson,1976-1978. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Lot 11527 - Papers of David J. Lyster,1981. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Lot 11537 - Papers of Elton and Ruby Coleman,1980. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Lot 11560 - Papers of Charlotte Moran and Eduardo Carrasco,1988-1991. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Lot 11594 - Papers of Judith T. Parker,1984. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Lot 11599 - Papers of William and Anna Sawyer,1911-1970. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Lot 11601 - Papers of Ina Jeanette Seigel,1974. (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Lot 11602 - Papers of Anthony St. Philip III,1985. (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Lot 11657 - Papers of the Grandis Family,1931-1934. (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Lot 11752 - Papers of Gwendolyn Mess Wythe,1988-1990. (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Lot 12250 - Papers of Helen and Mack Barlow,1922-1956. (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Lot 12252 - Papers of the Bird International Corporation,1976-1977. (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Lot 12254 - Papers of Jack Blount,1957-1983. (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Lot 12256 - Papers of Norma Brown,1975. (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Lot 12257 - Papers of Joseph and Patricia Carmine,1978. (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Lot 12258 - Papers of Gerald Chaffee,1971-1977. (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Lot 12260 - Papers of Prentice O. Dean,1982. (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Lot 12261 - Papers of Melvin Deaton,1954-1956. (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Lot 12263 - Papers of Gordon and Dawn Dixon,1978. (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Lot 12269 - Papers of Ernest Gordon, Jr.,1946-1980. (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Lot 12275 - Papers of Joseph Luciow,1946-1957. (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Lot 12277 - Papers of Robert Meadows,1921-1957. (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Lot 12279 - Papers of Joseph Miller,1978-1981. (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Lot 12284 - Papers of Gerald Parsons,1965. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Lot 12287 - Papers of Joan Powell,. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Lot 12288 - Papers of James W. Rawles,1951-1981. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Lot 12292 - Papers of Chester Robinson, Jr.,1944-1971. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Lot 12294 - Papers of Ronald Semones,. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Lot 12295 - Papers of Henry and Lillian Smith,. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Lot 12311 - Papers of Charles and Betty Anderson,. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Lot 12316 - Papers of Carrington and Sharyn Conley,1974. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Lot 12319 - Papers of Carl J. Ferraro, Jr.,1919-1974. (1 of 3) (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Lot 12319 - Papers of Carl J. Ferraro, Jr.,1945-1972. (2 of 3) (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Lot 12319 - Papers of Carl J. Ferraro, Jr.,1965-1972. (3 of 3) (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Lot 12323 - Papers of Clyde Harris,1963-1974. (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Lot 12325 - Papers of William E. Johnson,1954-1976. (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Lot 12328 - Papers of Virginia Jones and Percy Burt,1927-1973. (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Lot 12333 - Papers of Marietta and George Kemp,1922-1946. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Lot 12339 - Papers of Fanny L. Toney,1940-1954. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Lot 12340 - Papers of Charles H. Littleford,1957. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Lot 12345 - Papers of Ernest Rogers Mathews,1968. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Lot 12346 - Papers of Jimmie J. McClinney,1929-1940. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Lot 12357 - Papers of Edgar Nuckols,1929-1955. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Lot 12358 - Papers of Elwood Orkin,. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Lot 12362 - Papers of Jeffrey Petrey,1954-1975. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Lot 12368 - Papers of Minerva Ragland,1959-1961. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Lot 12370 - Papers of Alan Ralston,1942-1948. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Lot 12372 - Papers of Myrtle Reynolds,1928-1930. (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Lot 12378 - Papers of Rosa E. P. Robinson,1940-1976. (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Lot 12382 - Papers of Max Rucktaschel,1915-1930. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Lot 12390 - Papers of Fleet H. Scroggs,1937-1950. (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Lot 12393 - Papers of William Slaughter,1929-1940. (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Lot 12395 - Papers of Alexander Smith,1972. (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Lot 12401 - Papers of Emma Bizzelle and Mamie J. Loth,1893-1924. (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Lot 12403 - Papers of Thomas and Judith Stewart,1975. (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Lot 12405- Papers of Virginia Blake,1975. (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Lot 12406 - Papers of Mabel Spakes and B. F. Turner,1931. (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Lot 12410 - Papers of Jerome Kaye, Universal Development Corporation,1969-1970. (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Lot 12413 - Papers of Hildred Vernon and R. Alfred White,1944-1945. (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Lot 12416 - Papers of Leonard T. Wells,1938-1945. (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Lot 12427 - Papers of Donald Stokes,1968-1983. (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Lot 12435 - Papers of Claudia (Brennon) Gallo,1979. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Lot 12440 - Papers of Roy and Eva Herkimer,1912-1975. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Lot 12443 - Papers of David Lee Davis,1977-1980. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Lot 12446 - Papers of Robert and Robin Frye,1974. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Lot 12448 - Papers of James Harkins,1971-1982. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Lot 12455 - Papers of Bill and Sallie T. Jones,1960-1977. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Lot 12462 - Papers of Ronnie Clyde Maness,1983. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Lot 12463 - Papers of Claude Martin and Vivian Burnsed Martin,1911-1974. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Lot 12464 - Papers of Lawrence and Beatrice McKay,1964-1979. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Lot 12466 - Papers of Bonnie and Kenneth Michaud,1975-1982. (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Lot 12469 - Papers of Deborah Ann Preston,1979. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Lot 19470 - Papers of Robert and Donna (Parker) Rankin,. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Lot 12477 - Papers of Sadie L. Snyder,1954-1967. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Lot 12486 - Papers of McKinley and Ruth Meade,1919-1979. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Lot 12497 - Papers of Roger Williams Graham,1973-1985. (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Lot 12501 - Papers of Kenneth McMahon,1961-1987. (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Lot 12503 - Papers of Emanuel D. Williams,1939-1958. (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Lot 12507 - Papers of Holland and Louise Latham,1949-1977. (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Lot 12508 - Papers of Herbert T. Jackson,1883-1980. (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Lot 12511 - Papers of Fred Lenoir and Betty Lou Clark,1934-1955. (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Lot 12514 - Papers of Mary S. West,1910-1986. (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Lot 12517 - Papers of Miles M. Martin,1865-1953. (1 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Lot 12517 - Papers of Miles M. Martin,1944-1962. (2 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Lot 12517 - Papers of Miles M. Martin,1946-1960. (3 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Lot 12519 - Papers of Barbara C. Martin,1964-1986. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Lot 12528 - Papers of Roosevelt A. Goordon, Jr.,1983. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Lot 12532 - Papers of Jayne Kay Holsinger-Schumpert,1939-1980. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Lot 12539 - Papers of Edward and Penny Humbert,1987-1988. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Lot 12543 - Papers of Michael and Hawa Harmon,1976. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Lot 12545 - Papers of Bruce Richardson,1958-1959. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Lot 12546 - Papers of Eric and Deborah West,1975. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Lot 12561 - Papers of Richard and Karen Whitt,1979. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Lot 12562 - Papers of Millard Wagnon,1917-1921. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Lot 12589 - Papers of Michael Strickland and Mary Ann Campion,1986. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Lot 12591 - Papers of Luther Jennings,1945-1981. (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Lot 12608 - Papers of Julian Manuel Carver,1955-1972. (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Lot 12626 - Papers of Harry and Pauline Austin,1933-1979. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Lot 12629 - Papers of Samuel and Emma Powell,1953-1983. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Lot 12645 - Papers of Raymond and Flotilla Parker,1953-1984. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Lot 12651 - Papers of George and Charlotte Hudak,1974. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Lot 12659 - Papers of Doyle Bayes Johnson,1969-1970. (1 of 2) (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Lot 12659 - Papers of Doyle Bayes Johnson,1970. (2 of 2) (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Lot 12662 - Papers of William M. Davidson,1974. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Lot 12666 - Papers of Norman and Ronnie Barbara Cohen,1977-1981. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Lot 12670 - Papers of Carol and E. Montgomery Thomson,1967-1973. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Lot 12674 - Papers of C. W. Beattie,1909-1913. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Lot 12821 - Papers of Joseph and Ramona Kaplan,1974-1978. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Lot 12825 - Papers of John Blevins,1934-1974. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Lot 12833 - Papers of Edward Caine and Susan Power,1948-1983. (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Lot 12834 - Papers of Stephen Paul Engleberg,1958. (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Lot 12836 - Papers of Annie McCormick,1965. (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Lot 12841 - Papers of Donna Longerbeam,1964-1973. (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Lot 12842 - Papers of Helene Panayotidis,1973-1981. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Lot 12845 - Papers of Solomon and Sara Knaff,1961-1964. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Lot 12848 - Papers of William R. Robbins,1910-1978. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Lot 12852 - Papers of Mary Fields and Ruby Fields,. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Lot 12902 - Papers of Judith Evans Welch,1961-1981. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Lot 12904 - Papers of Barbara E. Falker,1976. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Lot 12905 - Papers of Orjay J. Robinson, Jr.,1971-1977. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Lot 12918 - Papers of Ajack and DaVine Scott,1948-1986. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Lot 12920 - Papers of Maurice T. Jones,1982. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Lot 12927 - Papers of Mary Beckham,1961-1978. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Lot 12932 - Papers of Mary Anette Bermingham,1945-1978. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Lot 12934 - Papers of Alvin and Robin Blakenship,1966-1977. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Lot 12938- Papers of John W. Boggs,1927-1979. (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Lot 12945 - Papers of Elvira Bryant and Larry Darnell Bryant,1982. (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Lot 12954 - Papers of Walter Lake Catron,1943-1961. (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Lot 12955 - Papers of O. Stuart Chalifoux,. (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Lot 12956 - Papers of Wesley D. Chatman,1978-1981. (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Lot 12960 - Papers of Michael and Kathryn Cleek,1979. (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Lot 12961 - Papers of Milton Cochran,1983-1984. (Box 55, Folder 19)